Guide to the Arthur Brown Papers SC0707
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Drawings, Accession ARCH-2006-256
  - Stanford Hospital Driveway Entrance Door, 1916 Oct 21 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Caddie Shelter, 1930 Jan 21 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Point of Compass (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford University and Vicinity Map, 1921 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford University and Vicinity Map, 1921 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Course Pro Shop, 1929 Nov 27 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Porch Rafters Eaves, 1930 Aug 04 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Hinged Sash, 1930 Aug 05 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Exterior Doors Frames, 1930 Aug 04 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Casements, 1930 Aug 05 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Interior, 1930 Sep 04 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Bolster Over Posts, 1930 Sep 04 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Porch Ballistrade, 1930 Sep 11 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Kitchen Tan Close Doors, 1930 Aug 06 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Door to Tell Booth, 1930 Sep 22 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Mantel Detail, 1930 Sep 15 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Grills for Radiator, 1931 Jan 12 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Plot Plan, 1930 Jul 08 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Basement Foundation Plan, 1930 Feb 08 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House First Floor Plan, 1930 Jul 08 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Roof Plan, 1930 Jul 8 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House West Elevation, 1930 Jul 08 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Sections, 1930 Jul 08 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Contour Map, 1930 May 20 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Heaters for Lounge Room (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Pumphouse, 1930 Jul 10 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Sketches for Golf House, 1923 Jul 11 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Golf House Floor Plan Elevations, 1929 Jul 26 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Foundation Plan, Footings and Section, 1929 Jul 26 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Revised Detail of Plank Filling Front Porch, 1930 Sep 08 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Concealed Heates for Lounge, 1930 Sep 16 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Pro Shop Interior Details, 1929 Nov 18 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Pro Shop, 1929 Nov 11 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Pump House, 1930 Jul 10 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Pro Shop, 1929 Nov 11 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Soda Fount. Details, 1930 Jul 26 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Plot Plan Caddie House (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Sash, 1930 Jul 28 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House French Windows, 1930 Jul 29 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Sliding Sash, 1929 Nov 11 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Golf Club House Rafters, 1929 Nov 11 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Outside, 1930 Apr 09 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Stairs and East Wall, 1930 Apr 09 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Trims, Windows, etc., 1930 Apr 09 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Exterior Stair, 1930 Jul 14 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Entrance Doors, 1930 Jul 26 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Entr Vestibule Office Lobby, 1930 Jul 30 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Swimming Pool Drains, 1930 Aug 09 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Main Entrance Elec. Outlets, 1930 Aug 11 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Conc. Details Gym Dance Studio, 1930 Aug 30 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Revised Plan of Colonnade, 1930 Aug 15 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Elect. Outlets in Colonnade, 1930 Aug 20 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Shower Rm. Details, 1930 Sep 02 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Section Through Shower Rooms, 1931 Oct 30 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Showers in Dress Rm., 1930 Sep 10 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Profile of Architrave, 1930 Sep 22 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Profile of Shower Roof, 1930 Sep 16 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Cast Stone Pyramids of Entrance Tower, 1930 Sep 18 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Detail of Skylight Admin. Wing, 1930 Sep 23 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Corridor Details, 1930 Sep 29 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Detail of High Window Colonnettes and Entr. Vestibulle, 1930 Oct 04 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Photographic Rooms, 1930 Sep 08 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Trim in Admin Wing, 1930 Oct 09 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Revised Paving Diagram, 1930 Oct 14 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Details of Kitchen Case, 1930 Oct 15 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Beam Ceiling in Dance Studio, 1930 Nov 11 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Paving Layout, 1931 Feb 17 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Paving Layout, 1931 May 08 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Ext. Door Frames/ Also Louvre Int. Access Dr., 1930 Jun 19 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Frames Windows in Locker Rm Wing Dr To Wading Pool Dr to Storage Rm, 1930 Jun 19 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Double Hung Window/ Windows in Entr. Vestibule Office Lobby, 1930 Jul 17 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Doors Frames, 1930 Jul 17 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Doors From Court, 1930 Jul 21 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Detail Doors Outside, 1930 Jul 22 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Detail of Doors From Office Lobby to Court, 1930 Jul 28 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Revised Transom Bar Interior Trim Around Openings at Main Entrance, 1930 Aug 25 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Door Frames and Transom Bar, 1930 Jul 29 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Doors from Gym to Locker Room, 1930 Aug 11 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Eaves Detail Admin Wing, 1930 Aug 07 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Rake Mold Admin Wing, 1930 Aug 07 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Rake Mold Small Gable Motif, 1930 Aug 07 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Eave of Small Gable Motif, 1930 Aug 07 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Rake Mold Locker Room, 1930 Aug 07 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Eaves Locker Room Wing, 1930 Aug 07 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Cornice of Entrance Court Gable Motif, 1930 Aug 11 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Rake Cornice of Entrance Court Gable Motif, 1930 Aug 11 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Eaves Dance Studio, 1930 Aug 12 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Rake Mould Cornice of Dance Studio, 1930 Aug 12 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Architrave of Colonnade, 1930 Aug 14 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Detail Tower Cornice, 1930 Sep 19 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Main Entrance Cast Col., 1930 Aug 09 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Cols at Main Entrance, 1930 Aug 20 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Int. Pier. Caps at Entr. Vestibule Office Lobby Doors, 1930 Aug 25 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Pier Cap Entr. To Court, 1930 Aug 23 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym 12 Faced Col. With Entasis, 1930 Sep 06 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Vestibule Col. Cap, 1930 Sep 19 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Door Frame to Stair # 3, 1930 Sep 12 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Detail of Large Vestibule Cols., 1930 Sep 08 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Seats in Small Gable Motif, 1930 Sep 23 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Ceil. Light Plaster Cornice in Lounge, 1930 Sep 26 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Ceil. Light in Office, 1930 Sep 26 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Ventilating Type Ceiling Light, 1930 Sep 26 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Full Size Interior Doors and Frames, 1930 Oct 01 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Colonnette at Million of Vestibule High Windows, 1930 Oct 03 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Colonnette at Million of Office Lobby High Windows, 1930 Oct 03 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Semicircular Seats, 1930 Oct 09 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Detail of Small Arches in Entr. Vest Office Lobby, 1930 Oct 08 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Detail Blackboard Chalk Rail Chair Rail Wanscot Cap, 1930 Oct 10 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym JAMB, 1930 Oct 14 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Leader Box, 1930 Oct 14 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Dance Studio Balcony Front, 1930 Oct 15 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Detail of Sliding Sash Counter, 1930 Oct 16 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Detail of Folding Mirrors in Corrective Clinic, 1930 Oct 21 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Pool Fountain in Court, 1931 Jan 30 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Benches in Court, 1931 Feb 05 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Mastic Joint in Swimming Pool, 1931 Sep 09 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Floor Plan, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Section and Elevation, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Floor Plan, 1928 Dec 04 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Section and Elevation, 1928 Dec 04 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Section and Elevation, 1928 Dec 28 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Shades and Reflectors (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Lamps (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Women's Gym Signet and Crown Operators for Top Pivoted Steel Sash, 1930 Sep 20 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Library 1917 Full Size Detail of Brick Jack Arches Easte Elevation, 1917 Jul 06 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Stanford LOEB Lab Roof Vents, 1927 Jul 15 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stanford LOEB Lab Sect. Thru Joints in Trench, 1927 Nov 30 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stanford LOEB Lab Front Entrance, 1927 Dec 13 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stanford LOEB Lab Detail of Main Stairs (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stanford LOEB Lab Window Frames and Sash (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stanford LOEB Lab Shutters in Dark Rooms, 1927 Feb 21 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stanford LOEB Lab Types L and O Sash Doors, 1927 Feb 21 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stanford LOEB Lab Exterior Sash Doors, 1927 Feb 21 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stanford LOEB Lab Shaft in Lab B, 1927 Feb 23 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stanford LOEB Lab Interior Doors Trim, 1927 Feb 24 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stanford LOEB Lab Inscription, 1927 Dec 13 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stanford LOEB Lab Inscription, 1927 Dec 13 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stanford LOEB Lab Inscription, 1927 Dec 13 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stanford LOEB Lab Inscription, 1927 Dec 13 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stanford LOEB Lab Inscription, 1927 Dec 13 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stanford LOEB Lab Inscription, 1927 Dec 13 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stanford LOEB Lab Stair Hall and Vestibule, 1927 Feb 27 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stanford LOEB Lab Selection Thru Cornice (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stanford LOEB Lab Wicket from Vestibule to Office, 1927 Jul 15 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stanford LOEB Lab Detail of Window Frames, 1927 Oct 3 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall # 3 Basement Frames in Conc Walls, 1922 Aug 12 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall # 3 Trunk Lift, 1922 Aug 15 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall # 3 Typical D H Windows, 1922 Sep 21 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall # 3 DH Windows Sitting Rooms No. 2 4, 1922 Sep 08 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall # 3 Entrance Lobby Frames, 1922 Sep 20 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall # 3 Alcove Frames, 1922 Oct 02 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall # 3 French Widnows Sitting Rooms 1 through 4 and Doors next to Sitting Rooms, 1922 Oct 09 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall # 3 Upper Windows in Side Walls of Assembly Hall, 1922 Oct 16 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall # 3 Third Floor French Windows, 1922 Oct 20 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall # 3 Arch Moulds, 1922 Oct 27 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall # 3 Arcade, 1922 Oct 30 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall # 3 Cornice of 2 Story Wings, 1922 Oct 30 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall # 3 Cornice Roof over Assembly Room, 1922 Oct 03 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall # 3 Cornice over 3 Story Portion, 1922 Nov 01 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall # 3 Cornice of Small Towers, 1922 Nov 01 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall # 3 Cornice of Large Towers, 1922 Nov 01 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall # 3 Louver Vents over Vent Shafts, 1922 Nov 03 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall # 3 Louver Vents in Gables of 3 Story Portion, 1922 Nov 04 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall # 3 Doors from Attics to Roofs, 1922 Nov 04 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall # 3 Windows in Rear Wall of Assembly Hall, 1922 Nov 28 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall # 3 Full Size Curves of Steps Stairway No 1, 1922 Dec 18 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall # 3 Curves of Steps 1,2,3,4 Stairway No.1, 1922 Dec 18 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall # 3 Curves of Steps Stariway No.1, 1922 Dec 19 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Elevation Section Mantel In Sitting Rooms, 1922 Nov 14 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Landing C at 2nd Floor, 1922 Dec 23 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Landing D Stairway No.1, 1922 Dec 27 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Section Door from Study to Corridors, 1923 Jan 04 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Doors form Bed Rooms Studys to Corridors, 1923 Feb 27 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Full Size Beam Details Assem Room Alcoves, 1923 Jan 24 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Ceiling Lights, 1923 Feb 09 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Details of Brick Wainscot in Assembly Hall, 1923 Feb 15 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Lobby Doors Trim Etc., 1923 Feb 19 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Details of Niche for Hose Racks in Corridors, 1923 Feb 26 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Details of Alcove Vestibules and Revised Hose Reel Cabinet, 1923 Mar 05 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Fixed Transom Bet Corridor Study No. 80 Third Floor, 1923 Mar 08 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Partition Bet Dressing Room and Sleeping Porch, 1923 Mar 30 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Sitting Rooms 2 4, 1923 Apr 09 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Section Thru Head of Book Cases Door to Door Corridor Sitting Rooms 1 3, 1923 Apr 27 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Vents in Doors, 1923 Apr 14 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Bedroom Details, 1923 Apr 19 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Details Stair Rails Newels, 1923 Apr 26 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Leader Boxes, 1923 May 02 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Door and Wicket to Office (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Balcony Rail Brackets in Assembly Hall Gallery, 1923 Aug 06 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Bay G Balcony Rail Assembly Hall Gallery, 1923 Aug 08 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Bay H Balcony Rail Assembly Hall Gallery, 1923 Aug 08 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 2nd Story Wiring for Carnegie Institution (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Headhouste for Greenhouses, 1928 Jan 19 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Laboratory Fixtures, 1928 Nov 26 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Main Stair Lavatory Under, 1928 Nov 23 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Hood In Lab 102, 1928 Dec 10 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Typical Window, 1928 Nov 28 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Entrance Doors Sideligths, 1928 Dec 03 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Cornice, 1928 Dec 04 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Interior Details, 1928 Dec 07 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Doors to Preparation House, 1928 Dec 10 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Tables and Drawers, 1928 Dec 14 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Partitions of Shop and Transoms in Rooms, 1928 Dec 14 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Revised Ceiling Main Entrance, 1923 May 01 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Archs (1 of 6) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Archs (2 of 6) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Archs (3 of 6) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Archs (4 of 6) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Archs (5 of 6) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Archs (6 of 6) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Details of Columns (1 of 3) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Details of Columns (2 of 3) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Details of Columns (3 of 3) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Archs with Columns (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Archs with Columns to Scale (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Doors (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Railings (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Cols. At Entrance, Arch to Sitting Rms and Entrance Arch of Archade, 1922 Oct 02 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Arcade and Sitting Room Window Cols, 1923 Apr 23 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Detail of Columns Third Floor Balconies, 1931 Oct 30 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Detail Columns at Main Entrance Arch, 1923 Apr 23 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Cols for Front Wing Towers, 1923 Jan 05 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Col's Main Entrance Towers, 1923 Jan 05 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Base for Columns in Entrance Lobby, 1923 May 09 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Colums of Assemply Hall Mantel, 1923 Mar 28 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Base Colonette on Breast of Mantel Assembly Hall, 1923 Aug 13 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Details for Base of Columns in Assembly Hall and Colums of Arches Bet Alcoves Assembly Hall, 1923 Sep 19 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Finished Floor Line of Columns in Gallery, 1923 Aug 03 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Detail of Capital A in Entrance Lobby, 1923 Apr 30 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Detail of Capital B in Entrance Lobby, 1923 May 01 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Detail of Capital C in Entrance Lobby, 1923 May 08 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Detail of Capital D in Entrance Lobby, 1923 May 08 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Detail of Capitals A B in Assembly Hall, 1923 Jul 18 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Detail of Capitals C D in Assembly Hall, 1923 Jul 19 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Corbel of Main Entrance, 1923 Aug 02 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Capital E Gallery in Assembly Hall, 1923 Aug 06 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Capital F Gallery in Assembly Hall (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #3 Capital K Colonette on Breast of Mantel Assembly Hall, 1923 Aug 13 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Cornice of 2 Story Wings, 1923 May 03 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Cornice Over 3 Story Center, 1923 May 03 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Balconies on East and West Elevs., 1923 May 07 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Fire Escape Balcony in Court, 1923 May 08 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Stationary Sash in Kitchen, 1923 May 04 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Living Room Interiors, 1923 Jun 06 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Mantel in Living Room, 1923 Jun 11 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Wood Doors in Entrance Lobby and Stair Hall #4, 1923 Jun 15 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Corridor Doors and Interior Trim, 1923 Jun 21 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Trim for French Windows at Ends of Corridors, 1923 Jun 23 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Trim Bedrooms Studies, 1923 Jun 25 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Details in Dressing Room and Sleeping Porch, 1923 Jun 27 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Entry to Corridors at 1st and 2nd Floors, 1923 Jun 28 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Ceiling Lights, 1923 Jul 02 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Stair Details, 1923 Jul 05 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Kitchen Doors, 1923 Jul 05 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Guard For Dumb Waiter Kitchen, 1923 Jul 06 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Tresholds and Plinths for Corridor Doors, 1923 Jul 11 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Docible Hung Windows Casement Sash and Doors, 1923 Feb 17 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Basement Frames, 1923 Feb 17 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Typical Double Hung Windows, 1923 Feb 19 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Double Hung Windows Kitchent, 1922 Feb 20 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Door Frames Kitchen Floor, 1923 Feb 21 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 French Sash in Living room and Entrance Lobby, 1923 Feb 21 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Arcade Frames, 1923 Feb (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Second Floor Sills French Doors at Ends of Corridors, 1923 Feb 24 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 French Windows French Sash Dining Room, 1923 Mar 08 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Door From Arcade Dining Room, 1923 Mar 10 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Large Windows Dining Room, 1923 Mar 13 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Brackets under Trusses Dining Room, 1923 Mar 14 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Circular Windows in Kitchen, 1923 Mar 14 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Doors from Dining Room to Kitchen and Office, 1923 Mar 19 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 French Windows (3rd Floor), 1923 Mar 20 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Sash in Sleeping Porches, 1923 Mar 21 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 In Bed Room 3rd Floor Access Doors to Attic, 1923 Mar 22 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Arcade Details, 1923 Mar 24 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Full Size of Stairs (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Dining Room Cornice (Exterior), 1923 Mar 27 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Full Size of Stairs No1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Stair No.6, 1923 Mar 30 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Interiors of Dining Room, 1923 May 02 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Res. Hall #4 Cornice of Kitchen Roof, 1923 May 02 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Carnegie Institution Lab Basement Plan, 1928 Nov 26 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Carnegie Institution Lab First Floor Plan, 1928 Nov 26 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Carnegie Institution Lab Second Floor Plan, 1928 Nov 26 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Carnegie Institution Lab East and West Elevations, 1928 Nov 26 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Carnegie Institution Lab North Elevation, 1928 Nov 26 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Carnegie Institution Lab South Elevation, 1928 Nov 26 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Carnegie Institution Lab Elevations and Sections, 1928 Nov 26 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Carnegie Institution Lab Typical Spandrel Sections, 1928 Nov 26 (Box 10, Folder 8)